hcgultradiet.com 2015-04-01

# HCG Ultra - Buy Now

"Ultra6 LLC" ("Ultra6 Nutrition LLC", "us" or "we"), has created this privacy policy (hereinafter the "Privacy Policy") in order to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices.  We understand the importance that internet users place on privacy and have designed our service with this in mind. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: 1) access or  use a "Ultra6 LLC website" (the "Website"); and/or 2) select and register for an offer(s) on the Website by clicking the offer(s) presented. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of  our Privacy Policy, please do not use or access the Website or its products/services. If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your  personal information to any third party for direct marketing purposes, please e-mail us at support@ultra6nutrition.com  1\. Information We Collect The information that we collect is generally limited to personal information about you that you submit on the Website. The personally identifiable information that may be collected includes:  your name; address; email address and telephone number. To the extent that customer credit card-specific information is collected by Ultra6 LLC and any of its affiliates and/or subsidiaries,  said information will be kept in confidence and will not be shared with any third parties without the customer's prior informed consent. Like most standard website servers, we use log files.  Log files track anonymous user information including, but not limited to, Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider ("ISP"), referring/exit pages, platform  type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. This information is tracked in order to analyze trends, administer the Website, track users' movements in the aggregate and gather broad  demographic information for aggregate use. The information tracked via log files is not linked to personally identifiable information except for IP addresses and source URL.  2\. Cookies The Website uses "cookies" to assign unique identifiers to your computer. The cookies we use are persistent files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive. Cookies may  be used to help save information on past activities and other preferences, so that you are not required to reenter information each time that you visit the Website, and to deliver content  specific to your interests.  3\. How We Use Your Information Any personal information that you supply to us remains your personal property. However, by submitting that information to Ultra6 LLC, you grant us the right to use your personal information  for any legal purpose including, without limitation: a) providing promotional offers to you via email advertising and/or online banner advertising; b) transferring the personal information that  you provided to a third party, when necessary, to receive a product, service, or information that you may have requested from such third party while using the Website; c) tracking  compliance with our Terms and Conditions; and d) for validation, suppression, content improvement and feedback purposes. By submitting your information to the Website, you grant Ultra6  LLC the right to use that information for marketing purposes, and agree to receive email marketing from the Website. We may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. In order to  end your email subscription to a particular list, you must follow the instructions contained in any email correspondence that you receive from Ultra6 LLC. Unsubscribing from one list will not  automatically unsubscribe you from all email lists. We only send email marketing to individuals that have agreed, whether by visiting this Website or through third party websites, to receive  email marketing from Ultra6 LLC or its affiliates and partners. Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may be required to disclose personal information in some instances,  such as: 1) when required by law wherein we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, and/or subpoena; 2) in the event that  Ultra6 LLC is sold or acquired; or 3) in the event that we believe  that the Website is being, or has been, used in violation of our terms and conditions or to commit unlawful acts. Moreover, you hereby consent to the disclosure of any record or  communication to any third party when Ultra6 LLC, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your email address with other third  parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the provisions of the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time-to-time. We may share, license or sell your information to third  parties for various marketing purposes, including but not limited to e-mail marketing, telemarketing, text messaging, and direct mail.  4\. Sharing of Information Ultra6 LLC provides you with the opportunity to receive special offers, products and/or services from other third-party companies. To receive such offers, products and/or services your  personally identifiable information supplied to us during the registration process will be shared with such third-party companies so that they may provide the product or service to you that  you have ordered from them without requiring that you first complete another registration form. By submitting your e-mail address at the Website you agree to receive e-mail marketing from  Ultra6 LLC and our third-party advertisers. We may share our user information and/or join together with other businesses to bring selected opportunities to our users. We are able to offer  third party services to you, in part, based on your willingness to be reached by our third-party advertisers. In addition, you agree that such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry and/or an  application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 C.F.R. 310, et seq. (the "ATSR"). Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade  Commission's Do-Not-Call List, Ultra6 LLC retains the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR. Moreover, by registering with, or requesting information from, a  third-party advertiser at or through the Website, such action shall constitute a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application with the respective third-party advertiser for purposes of the ATSR  and you may be contacted via e-mail, direct mail and/or telemarketing by such third-party advertiser in accordance with the ATSR. Ultra6 LLC is not responsible for any content, terms and  conditions, or the privacy policies of any third party advertisers' websites. The entities that advertise and/or place banner ads at the Website including, but not limited to, third party  advertisers, are independent third parties and are not affiliated with Ultra6 LLC.  5\. Minors Visitors under 18 years of age are not permitted to use and/or submit their personal information at the Website. Ultra6 LLC does not knowingly solicit or collect information from individuals  under the age of 18. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.  6\. Security All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. Furthermore, access to this information is strictly limited, and the information is not accessible to the  public. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all Ultra6 LLC user information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct  use of information, we use appropriate industry standard procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewall, encryption, token authentication,  application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. In addition, Ultra6 LLC has security measures in place to  protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control. Please be advised that, although we take every reasonable technological precaution available to protect  your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  7\. Opting Out To stop receiving future communications from Ultra6 LLC, please visit our Unsubscribe Page. To unsubscribe from a third party service, you must contact that third party directly.  8\. Changes to the Privacy Policy & Notification of Changes Ultra6 LLC reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice at the Website that we are changing our Privacy Policy. If the manner in which we use  personally identifiable information changes, we will notify users by posting the changes on this Website. Any and all changes to our Privacy Policy are effective immediately upon posting.  The user's continued use of the Website and/or continued receipt of Ultra6 LLC e-mails constitutes an affirmative acknowledgement and acceptance by the user to the terms of the modified  Privacy Policy.  9\. Contacting Us If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of Ultra6 LLC please feel free to contact us at support@ultra6nutrition.com.

Privacy Policy:

Home | Privacy Policy | Terms & Conditions | Contact Us | [Mobile Site](http://m.hcgultradiet.com/) © Copyright 2015 Ultra6 Nutrition, LLC. All rights reserved.

This product is not for use by or sale to persons under the age of 18. This product should be used only as directed on the label. It should not be used if you are pregnant or nursing.  Consult with a physician before use if you have a serious medical condition or use prescription medications. A Doctor's advice should be sought before using this and any supplemental  dietary product. All trademarks and copyrights are the property of their respective owners and are not affiliated with nor do they endorse HCG Ultra Diet Drops or Ultra6 Nutrition, LLC.  These statements have not been evaluated by the FDA. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease. Individual weight loss results will vary. By using this  site you agree to follow the Privacy Policy and all Terms & Conditions printed on this site. Void Where Prohibited By Law. We are not affiliated with Dr. Mehmet Oz, ZoCo Productions LLC  or to ZoCo 1 LLC. ZoCo 1 LLC is the owner of the following trademarks: DR. OZ™, ASK DR. OZ™ and THE DOCTOR OZ SHOW™
